So I asked deep seek to, for the French thing, right? Again, so I say, hey deep seek,
I'm trying to learn French and I know nothing about it. All I know is English and I'm just getting
started. So start teaching me with the most used phrases in the language. Let's go.
And what else? For example, I want to convert my voice into text. It seems to be impossible
over here because I don't see the option, right? So I go with a command, I send it to
see what we get.
Yes, so as you see it says, excellent. I'm thrilled to be your guide on this adventure.
And as you see, we're going further. So it gives me a table. It says,
Yep. And yes, as you see, it goes even further, right? So you see that it's working really hard
on the topic that we just gave it. And yes, AI generated for reference only, yep. So when does it end?
Yeah, so it's done. As you see, there's a lot that it did for us with the first command.